I am already a prisoner.
I will be executed soon.
Why are you here?
To show off?
Princess Xiyao wants to see you.
I'm just accompanying her.
Otherwise,
when have you ever known me to pity a defeated opponent?
Princess Xiyao.
You are my princess consort.
You should have shared life and death with me.
Why did you collude with Su Zhiye so quickly?
Yuwen Jia, show some respect.
I'm going back to Rouran.
My good brother really knows how to win people's hearts.
It has nothing to do with Prince Shuo.
The marriage alliance has been put on hold.
I have no reason to stay anymore.
Since you admit that we are husband and wife,
I can beg His Majesty to pardon you.
It's useless.
Even my own sisters and aunts
don't hold that much weight in his heart,
let alone a woman from beyond the Great Wall like you.
You can go back to Rouran with me,
as long as you promise never to return to the Central Plains.
For the sake of good relations between the two countries,
they will definitely agree.
Yuwen Jia!
Don't do anything stupid.
Why?
What did I do wrong?
Yuwen Jia, calm down.
Let her go.
What emperor's destiny?
What exactly did I do wrong?
Tell me.
Calm down.
Even if I go to the underworld...
I will fight the Ten Kings of Hell for it.
Su Zhiye.
I have no interest in her.
Prepare a fast horse for me.
I'll let her go once I'm out.
Yuwen Jia, the horse is ready.
Let Xiyao go.
Zhiye.
I dare not delay the investiture ceremony.
But leaving you alone to deal with Yuwen Jia,
I'm really worried.
I've searched everywhere I should.
I even ransacked the Shang family's secret room.
Where else could he hide?
He didn't leave the city.
Could he be trying to ruin the investiture ceremony?
Read the decree. Prince Shuo, Yuwen Jingxuan, is outstanding in appearance
and possesses both virtue and merit. In strict accordance with the will of Heaven
and the sentiments of the people,
we respectfully inform the Heavenly Emperor, the ancestral temple, and the state.
He is hereby established as the Crown Prince,
granted the imperial seal and edict,
and takes his rightful place in the Eastern Palace.
Catch the assassin.
Kill on sight.
Zhiluo.
It's okay. I'll call the imperial physician right away.
Imperial physician!
It's no use.
It's no use, Jingxuan.
I don't want this.
We just got our memories back.
You can't just leave me like this.
Jingxuan.
Don't be sad.
This is fate,
but I don't regret it.
I never regretted meeting you,
and I never regretted falling in love with you.
Promise me.
You must be a...
A virtuous and wise ruler.
When the world is at peace,
and everyone is happy,
we will meet again.
I promise you.
The world at peace,
and everyone happy.
I will be a virtuous and wise ruler.
It's been less than a year since Jingxuan took the throne,
and the whole imperial capital has a new look.
I suppose it won't be long
before your promise to her
of a peaceful world
and universal happiness
comes true.
Hot
steamed buns!
Are you hurt?
No, I was careless. I apologize.
I'm very sorry.
I have to rush out to attend a lecture.
I'll take my leave first.
Looking at his clothes,
he doesn't look like he can afford a private school.
Let's follow him and find out.
I met you often in the mansion of Prince Qi,
And heard you several times in Cui Jiu's hall.
The scenery of Jiangnan is truly beautiful,
Meeting you again in the season of falling flowers.
Zhiluo.